bdjobs.com 2018-08-15

# bdjobs.com :: Largest Job Site in Bangladesh

**Bdjobs.com** collects information about visitors. This information includes your IP address, browser type, domain names, access times and referring addresses. We use this information for operating our services, maintaining the quality of the service, security management and providing reports for relevant business purposes. 

Confidentiality and Security We regard your CV as a very personal document and we wish you to have full control over who can view it and whether or not. 

The level of control is provided to you by your choice of whether to make your CV searchable by our Clients or not. Making your CV searchable considerably increases your exposure to potential employers. 

• When you apply to jobs through our services, your resume in your MYBDJOBS account and any other information that you disclosed during your job applications will be made available to the companies you are applying to. 

• You may block any employer not to access your CV from our database. 

• You may remove your CV from our searchable database at any time from "Delete Resume" option at MYBDJOBS. 

• We limit access to personal information about you to employees who we believe reasonably need to come into contact with that information to provide products or services to you or in order to do their jobs. If any recruiter is found to be breaching our terms and conditions, then we will immediately terminate their use of our services. 

Email Resume Our Email Resume service provides facility for MYBDJOBS account holder to email his/her detail resume to employer with message.

E-Mail this job to a friend Our Mail-a-Friend service makes it easy for our users to recommend jobs to friends or relatives. Simply complete the Mail-a-Friend form and we will send an email to your specified recipient(s) containing detail job description to the selected job. We will not use your recipient's details for any other purpose than the fulfillment of this service. 

Resume References In reference section to your resume, Bdjobs.com will ask you for their names, telephone numbers, emails and position titles. This information will be enclosed as part of your job application and employers may contact them to get references for your applications. 

Job Mail Service The Job Mail Service matches job seekers requirements for employment with the vacancies advertised on any one of our websites. For job seekers who register to this service you receive an email listing those jobs that we believe you should be interested in. Your requirements are defined by your preferred criteria which can be used to specific job titles, skills, organization types or other definition of the job you want. You can change these criteria at any time. 

E-Mail Notification Services When you subscribe to a Bdjobs.com E-mail Notification, We use your email address to send you the notification(s) you have requested like Bdjobs.com Newsletter, Bdjobs.com workshop/Training, Third Party offers and Promotions. You may subscribe and unsubscribe services by following the prominent instructions mentioned in each of the notification. 

Third-Party Tracking Technologies Bdjobs.com uses the Google Analytics tracking technology to track visits to our website. It allows us to analyze the usage of our website and is merely for our internal use. 

Cookies and Other Tracking Technologies  Some of our Web pages utilize "cookies" and other tracking technologies. A "cookie" is a small text file that may be used, for example, to collect information about Web website activity. Some cookies and other technologies may serve to recall Personal Information previously indicated by a Web user. Most browsers allow you to control cookies, including whether or not to accept them and how to remove them. 

You may set most browsers to notify you if you receive a cookie, or you may choose to block cookies with your browser, but please note that if you choose to erase or block your cookies, you will need to re-enter your original user ID and password to gain access to certain parts of the Web website. Our use of cookies and other tracking technologies allows us to improve our website and your web experience. Your IP address might be used to track your location to provide you with various location based services and for our data analysis purposes. We may also analyze information that does not contain personal information for trends and statistics. 

Security We use lots of tools (encryption, passwords, and physical security) to protect your personal information against unauthorized access and disclosure. 

Opting out of E-Mail Notification Services We allow users to opt-out of having Email Notification Alerts sent to them at any time. 

Revision and updates Bdjobs.com regularly revises and updates its privacy policy and publishes changes to the policy at our website.
